<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Desktop App Installation on Headlamp</title>
    <link>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Desktop App Installation on Headlamp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright the Headlamp project contributors</copyright><atom:link href="https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Linux Installation</title>
      <link>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/linux-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/linux-installation/</guid>
      <description>Currently we ship a Linux desktop application in two formats: Flatpak , and AppImage .
Flatpak  Flatpak gives an isolated and bundled way of running Headlamp, with decoupled runtime updates (besides other benefits ).
You need to make sure that Flatpak is installed in your Linux distro.
For installing Headlamp as a Flatpak, follow the instructions in its Flathub page .
For running it, just launch it as usually in your Linux desktop, or run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS Installation</title>
      <link>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/mac-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/mac-installation/</guid>
      <description>Install via brew Package Manager If you are using the Homebrew package manager , you can install the latest release like so:
brew install --cask headlamp Install via GitHub Releases For Mac OS we provide a .dmg file, so you need to download it from the releases page and than follow the below steps :
 Double click the downloaded file to make its content available (name will show up in the Finder sidebar), usually a window opens showing the content as well Drag the application from the DMG window into /Applications to install wait for the copy process to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Installation</title>
      <link>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/win-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/win-installation/</guid>
      <description>For Windows we provide a .setup.exe installer, so you need to download it from the releases page and follow its installation steps (after the installation, you should see Headlamp&amp;rsquo;s icon on your desktop).
Important: While running Headlamp, if Windows Defender prompts you about stopping the app because it&amp;rsquo;s from an unknown source, that happens because Headlamp&amp;rsquo;s Windows builds are not yet signed (we&amp;rsquo;re working on it). You can still run the app by choosing &amp;ldquo;Run Anyway&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running in headless mode</title>
      <link>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/headless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kinvolk.github.io/headlamp/docs/latest/installation/desktop/headless/</guid>
      <description>Some users prefer running Headlamp using the desktop app, but directly in their web browser instead of the Electron&amp;rsquo;s environment as this allows them to leverage the browser&amp;rsquo;s functionality such as bookmarks, groups, etc.
Running Headlamp in the system&amp;rsquo;s browser can be done by using the --headless CLI option. Assuming the have already downloaded and installed Headlamp on your desktop, you can run it in headless mode as follows:
Example:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
